

Daniel Justiz

Graphic & Web Designer

Miami, FL, USA

MY OBJECTIVES

With over 6 years of design experience I am confident I can be of great value to your business. My experience has given me a deep understanding of marketing strategies, design principles, and a strong foundation in custom website writing.

PERSONAL

danieljustiz9508@gmail.com

305-798-7451

danieljustizv 2. heroku app. com

Adobe Portfolio - https://danieljustiz.

LinkedIn - linkedin.com/in/daniel-justiz

Git - github.com/danielJ305

Behance - behance.net/danieljustizMedia/

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

Javascript, HTML, CSS/SASS

Libraries & Frameworks:

JQuery, Bootstrap

Tools & Platforms:

Git, Wordpress, CPanel, WPEngine

Design

Adobe: Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign

LANGUAGE

Spanish English 0% 100%

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2021 - Present Freelance Graphic Designer Web Designer UPWORK

Oct 2019 - May 2021 Web Designer & Content Creator FREIGHT HUB GROUP

Feb 2015 - Aug 2018 Web Designer & Social Media Manager NATURE ZONE TRADING

Feb 2015 - Aug 2018 Graphic Designer FREELANCING

RESPONSIBILITIES:

My work at Upwork extends from web design to graphic design. I built Custom/Wordpress Single Page Websites hosted on WP Engine or Elementor.

I have helped clients with their MailChimp API Integration and managed their email campaigns. I have also done much graphic design works such as T-shirts, logos, banners, posters and more.

RESPONSIBILITIES:

While working for Freight Hub Group (gofreighthub.io) I had the responsibility of administering over 12 websites, all on the WordPress platform. I had the key role of creating many of the conversion and sales funnel pages for different departments of the company as well as revamping custom-written websites, planning and implementing new features, developing their SEO structure, delivering new websites, optimization, and graphic design.

RESPONSIBILITIES:

Oversaw the marketing and maintained the social media outlets of the company.

Construction and maintaining of the company's website with Wix.

RESPONSIBILITIES:

Logos, banners, magazines, invitations, stationeries and custom illustrations.

Interacted with clients very often and made great professional relationships.

EDUCATION

2009 - 2013 High School High Shcool Diploma Miami Coral Park Senior High

INTERESTS

Fishing - Outdoors - Traveling - Photography - Foodie - Exercise & More...